### **CURRICULUM VITAE**

# Anjani Priyadarshini

Sr. Web Developer / React

Personal Details: DOB: 05-09-1985

Sex : Female

Nationality : Indian City : Hyderabad

# Objective

To acquire a position in a company that would allow me to be creative and keep me challenged with various web projects that require employing the latest trends and technologies.

Employing my passion on a multitude of design work, especially online design & develop! Enable to constantly learn, develop in varying areas of web development.

Having 9+ years of experience in development of Web applications using HTML 5 Sass, JavaScript and other frame works like Angular 2+, React Js Bootstrap, materialize css. Aspiring for a career in a professional organization where I can apply my varied thoughts for the fulfillment of the organization objectives and to scale greater heights along with the organization.

### Education

Completed **BA** from Kasturba Gandhi college in 2005, with an aggregate of 61.26% from Osmania University.

#### Skill Set

#### Skilled in:

HTML HTML5 CSS

CSS3 Photoshop CS6 Dreamweaver CS6
W3C Standards XHTML Mobile Website
React Frameworks Designs/Development
Illustrator CS6 Responsive Template Designs

### Knowledgeable in:

JQuery JavaScript Bootstrap Framework

Foundation Framework Wordpress Framework Eclipse

CorelDraw X5 JQuery Mobile themes
Mac xcode Responsive Design

### Work Experience

Company : QUAQUA Tavel Experiences pvt,Ltd.

Current Position : Sr. Web Developer
Duration : Dec 2017 to till date

Responsibilities : HTML , Responsive web designing, React

components, Quality Analyst etc.

# **Project**

Title - Quaqua Product

Role - Sr.Software Engineer

#### Team Size - 3

Technologies - React, HTML 5, CSS 3.

### **Description:**

QuaQua is a digital experience platform that integrates 360-degree virtual reality content for the global travel and tourism industry.

We strive to translate world's travel experiences into captivating 360 videos and AR/VR stories to provide real and immersive end to end travel experiences.

### Responsibilities.

Responsible for the architecture design and involved in high and low-level design of the individual components. Responsible for setting coding standards in the application.

Working with Team in Implementing and taking the In Charge for Quality Testing.

- Experience in working with Angular 2/4 modules, services, templates, directives, services and dependency injection to create a SPA.
- Hands on Experience on Angular CLI (Command line Interface).
- Expertise in using React JS components, Forms, Events, Keys, Router concept.
- Worked on some of the new features of Angular 4 like new if else syntax, ngtemplates, form validators.

### **Key Challenges**

Worked on new frame work with the support of a Technical Lead.

#### Websites & Mobile sites

https://www.quaqua.com/ https://m.quaqua.com/

# **Work Experience**

Company : PurpleTalk India (p) ltd, Hyderabad

Current Position : Front End Developer/ UI designer

Duration : Dec 2011 to Oct 2017

**Responsibilities** : Designing of web sites, Mobile apps, Web sites and

applications, Html Works, Responsive, Browser

Compatibility, UI Designs, etc.

# **Projects**

Title - GE - Knowledge Sharing

Role – Sr.UI Developer

**Duration – October 2016 – September 2017** 

Team Size - 4

**Technologies** – Angular JS , Javascript, HTML 5, CSS 3.

### **Description:**

This is a group of GE internal applications which consists of a mobile application and few web applications which are used to view the statistics of the corresponding device or requirement.

### Responsibilities.

Working to modify the existing code base as per the clients need and guiding the team which work on other web application. Make the code reviews and optimize the code for better maintain and performance of the app. Created Webparts in share point using share point designer

### **Key Challenges**

Worked on new frame work with the support of a Technical Lead.

### Project -2

Title - Magellan

Role - Module Lead

**Duration** – Feb 2015 – Aug 2016

Team Size - 4

**Technologies** –CSS, Java Script, Web Services, Android and IOS/ web application.

### **Description:**

We move beyond the traditional by delivering behavioral health and employee assistance program services; specialty health, including musculoskeletal, cardiac, advanced imaging management and physical medicine; and integrated care management to health plans, employers, Medicaid, Medicare and the Federal government.

### Responsibilities.

Responsible for the architecture design and involved in high and low-level design of the individual components. Responsible for setting coding standards in the application.

Working with Team in Implementing and taking the In Charge for Quality Testing.

### **Key Challenges**

Worked on Issues related to Process flow Orchestration Module where the entire business is depended.

#### **Main Contribution**

Client Implementation work is handled. Implemented as per the client requirements. Also involved in code review. Played an active role as mentor for group of developers.

# Project -3

Title - UHCOMW

Role - Sr Developer

Duration - March 2013 - Feb 2015

**Team Size** - 6

**Technologies** –CSS, Java Script, Web Services, Team Foundation Server 2010.

#### **Description:**

If you're a teen or young adult who's getting ready to live on your own, UnitedHealthcare OMW<sup>TM</sup> (UnitedHealthcare On My Way) is for you. You'll learn what it takes be independent. Like finding housing, getting a good job, managing your money – and more. It's easy. It's fun. And it's all right here.

Main Role generating Icon Fonts. Converting forms into pdf online generator. Unit Testing the project before Uploading to the sever.

#### **Architecture Details**

This project was implemented in multi-languages Using Bootstrap frame work and Javascript.

### Responsibilities.

Responsible for on time delivery for client. Giving Appropriate Estimations for the required Project paln. Design and involved in high and low-level design of the individual components. Responsible for setting coding standards in the application.

### **Key Challenges**

Performance tuning of the queries and created an mobile application and Responsive web site..

### **Main Contribution**

Implemented functionality of a classic website to the Current website ,which will decrease the maintenance cost of the application to the organization.

Also involved in code review. Played an active role as mentor for group of developers.

### Project - 4

**Title** – Option Monster

Role – Sr UI Developer

**Duration – July 2012 – February 2013** 

Team Size - 4

Technologies – HTML 5 CSS3, Mobile and Web Application, Jquiry Mobile /UI

### **Description:**

It's all about Trade marketing. It is a Cross-platform App. Built in jQuery Mobile framework takes the "write less, do more" mantra to the next level: Instead of writing unique applications for each mobile device or OS, the jQuery mobile framework allows you to design a single highly branded responsive web site or application that will work on all popular smartphone, tablet, and desktop platforms.

#### **Architecture Details**

This project was implemented in Day and Night based on Theme Roller in jQuery UI.

### Responsibilities.

Responsible for the architecture design and involved in high and low-level design of the individual components. Responsible for setting coding standards in the application.

### **Key Challenges**

Performance tuning of the queries. Also created UI/UX . Designing for Android and IOS applications also for responsible view.

#### **Main Contribution**

Also involved in Design review. Played an active role as mentor for group of developers. Co-ordinating with the Team.

### Project - 5

**Title** – rockfordfosgate.com

**Role** – UI Developer

**Duration - Dec 2011 - June 2012** 

Team Size - 2

**Technologies** – Photoshop cs, Illustrator, Icon Conversion.

### **Description:**

#### **ROCKFORD FOSGATE AUDIO FOR FANATICS!**

For over 35 years Rockford Fosgate has made lifestyle products that deliver the best audio experience in cars, boats, and recreational vehicles. We build our car audio subwoofers, car speakers and car amplifiers to fit your ride and music taste, while we design our moto-marine products to be element ready solutions for marine audio, motorcycle audio and UTV audio systems.

#### **Architecture Details**

This project was implemented in Photoshop for designing. Logo designing and icon creations in Illustrator.

# Responsibilities.

Involved in Designing and back-end Development with wireframe supporting and design Guide lines. Developing and maintaining a project Plan. Working with mentor to ensure the project meets its business needs and delivery in time.

#### **Main Contribution**

Worked on Unit Testing and Design QC with in the Team.

# **Design Qualities**

Highly passionate Determined

Self Motivated Able to work under pressure

Thinking out of box Offer varying styles

# **Personal Qualities**

Friendly Hardworking Willingness to Learn Optimistic

### Hobbies/Interest

Anything Design related Technology
Music Making friends

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned particulars are true to my knowledge.

Place: Hyderabad

Date: (Anjani Priyadarshini)